[
 
  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U77CdD3KP9o",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lAYJLqx3Suc",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Immortal"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/3gflA6flKig",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Diamond"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/sZfJFJJDniw",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Silver"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/Qa_LQgV9iDk",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Diamond"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/Wac1a_alQJQ",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Gold"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/rXHtMJ8s4TY",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Bronze"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R-PU1ngIJ2E",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Silver"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/-lh8AS8FC9o",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Diamond"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pQLYIuVT_ZQ",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Bronze"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/3Fq5fwJFm-0",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Bronze"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/LvkAGJSSPmQ",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Gold"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/9cZB-p6xwp4",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Platinum"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gBaVIewrRrg",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Platinum"
  },


  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yx7u8JasDVg",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/9nrPshQT6qY",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Gold"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/SM5Tzj82r9M",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Diamond"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/xWQkZ1Dd_9A",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Immortal"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/MOyracQDimw",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Bronze"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/7NzzvtZ_Y0M",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Diamond"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qh302iMYVJA",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Platinum"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mbbnouRxSw0 ",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Immortal"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/rSWH6ga61Zs",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Platinum"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FpjaL63kwv0",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Silver"
  },



  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/ws31TiFlyCo",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Gold"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/VWqRT2QPCrQ",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Iron"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MkCS3Fq0Xnk",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Platinum"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/dBUhKgJqLdc",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Platinum"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/xTKPskMluk4",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Gold"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/Oe1rsYI367I ",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Silver"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/Z_6D0S9DJeU",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Platinum"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/4CRHW1cnN-8",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Bronze"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/-o3lV4yGOTQ",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Platinum"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://youtu.be/LdUdjdGyEWw",
    "options": ["Iron", "Bronze", "Silver","Gold","Platinum","Diamond","Immortal","Radiant"],
    "correctAnswer": "Gold"
  }

]
